Guide to the Komen Foundation, Houston Records
University of Houston Libraries
Komen Foundation, Houston Records
1992-2012
1997-2008
02/2008-009
Susan G. Komen Breast Cancer Foundation. Houston Affiliate
36.00 linear feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
The Komen Foundation, Houston Records are housed in 35 boxes. The materials are arranged chronologically in ongoing yearly series with the following recurring subseries: Administrative Documents, Organizational Documents, Roster, Scholarships and Grants, Informational Material, Newsletters, Sponsors, Events, Race for Cure, Clippings and Correspondence, etc. Most notably, this collection documents organizational events and fundraising efforts from 1998 to 2012.
Historical Note:
In 1980, Susan Goodman Komen lost her battle with breast cancer at the age of 36. In the last months of Susan’s life, her sister, Nancy Goodman Brinker, made a promise to dedicate the rest of her life to increasing awareness and support of breast cancer research, education, screening and treatment. In 1982, Nancy’s promise launched the global breast cancer movement and the creation of the Susan G. Komen Breast Cancer Foundation, which was renamed Susan G. Komen for the Cure in 2009.
In 1990, Brinker established The Komen Houston Affiliate. It is ranked number one, topping 125 affiliate groups worldwide, in recognition of providing the most funding for education, screening and treatment both globally and in its seven-county service area in Southwest Texas. The Komen Houston Race for the Cure, the affiliate’s largest fundraiser, attracted a record 30,000 participants in 2008 amidst the devastation and confusion of the Hurricane Ike aftermath. As a grassroots network of breast cancer survivors and activists, the organization works to save lives, empower people, ensure quality care for all and energize science to find cures.
The Komen Foundation, as a whole, is the global leader of breast cancer awareness and support. As of 2008, the Susan G. Komen Breast Cancer Foundation had invested more than $1 billion since its inception in 1982. The Komen Foundation is the largest source of nonprofit funds dedicated to the fight against breast cancer in the world.
Sources:
www.komen-houston.org
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Susan G. Komen Breast Cancer Foundation. Houston Affiliate
Genre/Form of Material:
Brochures; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence; Fliers (printed matter); Newsletters; Posters; Sound recordings
Topical Term:
Breast -- Cancer; Nonprofit organizations -- Texas -- Houston
Accruals:
Additional materials were acquired in 2012 as part of a donation by Komen Foundation.
Additional materials were acquired in 2015 as part of a donation by Komen Foundation.
Acquisition Information
Information of acquisition method not available.
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research
Scope and Contents
The Komen Foundation, Houston Records are housed in 35 boxes. The materials are arranged chronologically in ongoing yearly series with the following recurring subseries: Administrative Documents, Organizational Documents, Roster, Scholarships and Grants, Informational Material, Newsletters, Sponsors, Events, Race for Cure, Clippings and Correspondence, etc. Most notably, this collection documents organizational events and fundraising efforts from 1998 to 2012.
Detailed List of Contents
- 1992-1996, id142379
  - Administrative Documents, id142387
    - Board Members, id142393 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Nominating Committee, id142394 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Events, id142388
    - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, id142396 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Trial Lawyer of the Year, id142397 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Dallas Award Luncheon Photographs, id142398 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Unknown Event Photographs, id142399 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Race for the Cure, id142389
    - Race 1995, id142401 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Race 1996, id142402 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Printed Publicity, id142390
    - News Clippings, id142404 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Various, id142391
    - H. Joan Ehlrich Background, id142406 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, id142407 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Photographs, id142408 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Various, id142409 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1997, id142380
  - Administrative Documents, id142410
    - Board Member Nominations, id142416 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Board Committee Report, id142417 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, id142418 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Nominating Committee, id142419 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Campaign, id142411
    - Annise Parker, id142421 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Candidates, id142422 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Donors/Fundraising, id142423 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Press Materials, id142424 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Race, id142412
    - Press Materials, id142426 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Photographs, id142427 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Events, id142413
    - “All in the Family”, id142429 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Luncheon, Washington, D.C., id142430 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Various, id142414
    - Articles, id142432 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- 1998, id73978
  - Administrative Documents, id74029
    - Board Correspondence, id74034 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Board of Directors; Thank You Letters, id74035 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Board Meeting, id142434 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Board Report, id142435 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - End of Year Report, id74036 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Grants, id74037 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Nominating Committee, id142436 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Rosters, id74030
    - Member Roster, id74038 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Mailing List, id74039 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Events, id74031
    - “Membership Coffee”, id74040 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - “Membership Reception”- Lolly Becker Home, id74041 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - “Membership Reception”- Junior League, id74042 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - “Membership Reception”-Photographs, id142440 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - “Membership Tea”- Mary Watters, id74043 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - River Oaks Reception Photographs, id142441 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Race 1998, id74032
    - Race Run up Preparation, id74044 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- 1999, id73979
  - Administrative Documents, id74046
    - Board Correspondence, id74055 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Board Chairmen, id74056 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, id142460 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Financial Documents, id142461 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Nominating Committee, id142462 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Organizational Documents, id74047
    - Houston Chapter Affiliate Agreement, id74057 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Newsletters, id74048
    - Komen Connection, id74058 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Frontline, id74059 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Development, id74049
    - Market Research, id74060 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Sponsor Contact List, id74061 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Sponsorship Request Correspondence, id74062 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Affiliate Organization Development Model, id74063 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Events, id74050
    - 1st Annual NE Houston Breast Cancer Awareness Reception, id74064 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 17th Annual Cancer Fighters Luncheon, id142467 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - BMW Ultimate Drive, id142468 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Celebrate 2000, id142469 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - “Membership Coffee”, id74065 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - “Membership Reception”, id74066 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - “Swinging Fore the Cure”, id142470 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Sydney Seaward Memorial Fund, id142471 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Tree of Life Foundation, id142472 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Unknown Event Photographs, id142473 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Race, id74051
    - Race Run-up Correspondence, id74067 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - General Race Meeting, id74068 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Race 1999 Brochure, id74069 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Printing Material, id74071 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Grants, id142475 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Race 1999, id142476 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Race 1999 (Pt. 1), id142477 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Race 1999 (Pt. 2), id142478 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Race 1999 (Pt. 3), id142479 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Race 1999 (Pt. 1), id142481 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Race 1999 (Pt. 2), id142482 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Photographs, id142483 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Photographs, id142484 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Poster, id142486 (Ovs box 32, Item 9)
- 2000, id73980
  - Administrative Documents, id74077
    - Steering Committee Minutes, id74089 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, id74090 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meetings, id74091 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - IRS Tax Exempt Status, id74092 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Financial Documents, id74093 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Advisory Board, id142488 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Nominating Committee, id142489 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Grants Progress Report, id74094 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Grants (Pt.1), id142490 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Grants (Pt.2), id142491 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Grants (Pt.3), id142492 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Grants (Pt. 1), id142494 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Grants (Pt. 2), id142495 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Organizational Documents, id74078
    - By-laws, id74098 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Timeline, id74099 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - North Jersey Affiliate Brochure, id74100 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Rosters, id74079
    - Board Members, id74101 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Race Roster, id74102 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sponsor, id74080
    - Race 2000 Corporate Teams, id74103 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Sponsorship Material, id74104 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Sponsor Contact List, id74105 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Events, id74106
    - “Survivor party”; RSVP & Invitation, id74108 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Sponsor Party, id74109 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - “Pink Ribbon Reception” & Mailing List, id74110 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Komen Affiliate Awards, id74111 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Houston BMW Group, id142500 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Explorer Giveaway, id142501 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Various Photographs, id142502 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Race, id74081
    - Race Script, id74112 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Sponsorship Form & Brochure, id74113 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Volunteer Information, id74114 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Photographs, id142506 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Photographs, id142507 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Patty Stone Program (Pt. 1), id142508 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Patty Stone Program (Pt. 2), id142509 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Patty Stone Program, id142510 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Doctors for the Cure, id142511 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Marsha Eckermann, id142512 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Event Guide (Pt. 1), id142513 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Event Guide (Pt. 2), id142514 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Various Binder (Pt. 1), id142515 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Various Binder (Pt. 2), id142516 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Informational Material, id74082
    - Breast Cancer Informational Booklet, id74121 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Demographic Information & Statistics, id74122 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, id74083
    - Komen Weekly, id74123 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Komen Weekly, id74124 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Komen Weekly, id74125 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Komen Weekly, id74126 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Frontline, id74127 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Komen/Houston Newsletter, id142519 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Printed Publicity, id74084
    - Articles, id142521 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - News Clippings, id74128 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- 2001, id73981
  - Organizational Documents, id74130
    - Confidentiality Agreement, id74139 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Houston Chapter Affiliation Agreement, id74140 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Administrative Documents, id74131
    - Disclosure Statements, id74141 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Financial Documents, id74142 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Board Members, id74143 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Board Members Profile, id74144 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Nominating Committee Meeting, id74145 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 2001 Timeline, id74146 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, id74147 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Annual Report, id74148 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee, id142524 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, id142525 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Race, id74132
    - Race Agreement, id74149 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Race Day Details, id74150 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Race Correspondence, id74151 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Race Material, id74152 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Race Script, id74153 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - General Race Meeting Minutes, id74154 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Race 2001- Brochure, id74155 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Race 2001, id142527 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Photographs, id142528 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Newsletters, id74133
    - Frontline, id74156 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Komen Weekly, id74157 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Komen Weekly, id74158 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Komen Weekly, id74159 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Komen Weekly, id74160 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Mailing List, id74161 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Komen/Houston, id142530 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Events, id74134
    - Foley’s Cruise for Cure, id74162 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Lee Denim Day-Sample, id74163 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Lee Denim Day, id74164 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Pink Ribbon Reception, id74165 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Pink Ribbon Reception, id74166 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Health & Fitness Expo, id74167 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Sponsor Expo, id74168 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - BMW Ultimate Drive, id74169 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Sing for the Cure, id74170 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Debra Show, id142532 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Sponsor VIP, id142533 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Quilt, id142534 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - H. Joan Ehrlich, id142535 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Scholarships and Grants, id74135
    - Komen College Sponsorship Program, id74171 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Komen Fellowship, id74172 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Printed Publicity, id74136
    - Newspaper Clippings & Articles, id74173 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Promotional Literature, id74137
    - Affiliate Education Workbook, id74174 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- 2002, id73982
  - Administrative Documents, id74176
    - Board of Directors, id74186 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Financial Documents, id74187 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Order Form, id74188 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - BBB Questionnaire, id74189 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Organizational Information, id74190 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, id74191 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Office Lease Agreement, id74192 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Disclosure and Conflict of Interest Policy, id74193 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Sales Tax Exemption Status, id74194 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, id74195 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Communication Committee Meeting, id74196 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Grants, id142540 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Nominating Committee, id142541 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Communications Committee (Pt. 1), id142542 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Communications Committee (Pt. 2), id142543 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Printing Committee (Pt. 1), id142544 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Printing Committee (Pt. 2), id142545 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Events, id74177
    - Luncheon, id74201 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Olivia Newton-John Concert, id74202 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Women in Golf Day, id74203 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Cut-A-Thon, id74204 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Memorial Hermann Mammography Center Opening Ceremony, id74205 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - “Unique Lives Experience” Lecture Series, id74206 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Asian Women’s Health Symposium, id74207 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Komen Grass Root Public Policy Project, id74208 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - National Oncology Education Program, id74209 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - National Association of Hispanic Nurses, id74210 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - “The Market” Membership Event, id74211 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Wood Land Tennis Tournament, id74212 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Strasburger & Price Luncheon, id74213 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - “Women’s Life Insurance Society” Program, id74214 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - National Peace Foundation, id74215 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - City of Houston- Older Americans Month, id74216 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - 4th Nation Wide Shopping Weekend, id74217 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Sisters Block Walk, id74218 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - 1st Annual Nancy Ovens Memorial Luncheon, id74219 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Pink Tie Events Ball, id74220 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Komen Foundation, 20th Anniversary, id74221 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Pink Ribbon Reception, id74222 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Pink Ribbon Golf Tournament, id74223 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Houston Comets Breast Cancer Awareness Game, id74224 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Health Talk Meet, id74225 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - “Power of Promise Pin” Fundraising, id74226 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Chair’s Organizational Award, id142547 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Sponsors, id74178
    - JOMA Enterprises, id74227 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Pink Cowboys, id74228 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - BMW Ultimate Drive, id74229 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - British Petroleum, id74230 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Lee Denim Day, id74231 (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - Macy’s- Heart & Soul, id74232 (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - Bass Pro Shops, id74233 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Nordstrom, id74234 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Macy’s- Heart & Soul, id74235 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - The Club at Falcon Point, id74236 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Cinco Ranch High School Theatre Department, id74237 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Promotional Literature, id74179
    - Demographic Information, id74238 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Mother’s Day Tribute Card Program, id74239 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Komen College Scholarship Brochure, id74240 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, id74180
    - Komen Weekly, id74241 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Komen Weekly, id74242 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Komen/Houston, id74243 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Printed Publicity, id74181
    - News clippings, id74244 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - News clippings, id74245 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - News clippings, id74246 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Race, id74182
    - Race for Cure-Rome Affiliate, id74247 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Race Monitoring Report, id74248 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Race Brochure, id74249 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Komen Virtual Race for the Cure, id74250 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Race Script, id74251 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Race Draft, id74252 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Race Improvement Recommendations, id74253 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Race wrap-up meeting, id74254 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Photographs, id142555 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Minutes, id142556 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Power of a Promise, id142557 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Sponsorship Opportunities (Pt. 1), id142558 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Sponsorship Opportunities (Pt. 2), id142559 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Sponsorship Opportunities (Pt. 3), id142560 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Race Binder (Pt. 1), id142561 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Race Binder (Pt. 2), id142562 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Race Binder (Pt. 3), id142563 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- 2003, id73983
  - Administrative Documents, id74260
    - Affiliate Training Session, id74269 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors, id74270 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Office Procedures, id74271 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, id74272 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Financial Documents, id74273 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Board Retreat, id74274 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Job Responsibilities, id74276 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Job Responsibilities, id74277 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Communications, id74275 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Strategic Planning, id142566 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Race, id74261
    - Rome Affiliate Brochure, id74278 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Race for Cure Brochure, id74279 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Girl Scouts, id74280 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Race Day Activities Correspondence, id74281 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Timeline, id74282 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Race Merchandize Report, id74283 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Race Script, id74284 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - “Decorating for a Difference”, id74285 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Physical Arrangement, id74286 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Meeting Minutes, id142568 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Marshall Report, id142569 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Volunteers, id142570 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Photographs, id142571 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Roster, id142572 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Race Director, id142574 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Race Binder (Pt. 1), id142575 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Race Binder (Pt. 2), id142576 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Events, id74262
    - Pink Ribbon Reception RSVP & Invitation cards, id74289 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Affiliate Conference, Arlington, TX, id74290 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lunch & Learn, id74292 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Grant Recipients- Pink Ribbon Café, id74293 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - The Power of a Promise, id142578 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Newsletters, id74263
    - Komen/Houston, id74294 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Komen weekly, id74295 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings, id74296 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Promotional Literature, id74264
    - Sponsorship Opportunity Brochure, id74297 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Printed Materials, id142564
    - Articles, id142582 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Life Cycle Report, id142583 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Various, id142584 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- 2004, id73984
  - Administrative Documents, id74299
    - Steering Committee Minutes, id74308 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Board Meetings, id74309 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Job Descriptions & Responsibilities, id74310 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Denver Affiliate, id74311 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, id74312 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Public Relations, id74313 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Komen Survivor Committee, id74314 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Request for Proposal, id74315 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Balance Sheet, id74316 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Affiliate President’s Guide, id142586 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Board of Directors, id142587 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Events, id74300
    - Survivor Party, id74318 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Pasta Party Pledge Program, id74319 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - High School Challenge, id74320 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Pink Honor Roll, id74321 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Pink Ribbon Café, id74322 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Pledge Program, id74323 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Rothko Chapel 40th Anniversary, id142589 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Sponsors, id74301
    - Kroger, id74324 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Tourneau, id74325 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Coca Cola, id74326 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Fiji Water, id74327 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Hyatt Regency, id74328 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Alief Independent School District, id74329 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Chevron Texaco, id74330 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Foley’s, id74331 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Marathon Oil, id74332 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Houston Chronicle, id74333 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Compass Bank Sponsorship, id74334 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Cordua, id74335 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Clear Channel, id74336 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Lester & Sue Smith Foundation, id74337 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Fleet Feet, id74338 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Race, id74302
    - Timeline, id74339 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Script, id74340 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - Banners, id74341 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Banners, id142594 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Registration Forms, id74342 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Parking Arrangements, id74343 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Statistics, id74344 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Decorations, id74345 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - News Commentary, id74346 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Contracts, id74347 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Permit Request Documents, id74348 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Route Maps, id74349 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Logo, id74350 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Marshal Meeting & Correspondence, id74351 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Photography Correspondence, id74352 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Partner Toolkit, id74353 (Box 11, Folder 12)